Since we're looking for this embryonic power,
この胚の力を探しに行くのであれば、
we must align ourselves with this embryonic power.
この胚の力に身を置かなければなりません。
It's like a radio frequency, you see, where I'm looking for that frequency.
それはラジオの周波数のようなもので、その周波数を探すようなものです。
For this, we will learn to observe the patient's breathing.
そのためには、患者さんの呼吸を観察することを学びます。
Really observe it, the patient's first breath.
本当に、患者さんの最初の呼吸を観察します。
And little by little, we will look for a point, a door,
そして少しずつ、私たちはある点、ある扉を探しに行きます。
where we will deposit our sensation.
そこに私たちの感覚を置きます。
which is at the end of the exhale and before the inhale.
それは呼気の終わりで、吸気の前にあります。
Let's do this exercise together already to simply discover a quality of the mind.
まず、心の質を単純に発見するために、この練習を一緒に行いましょう。
You will all join me.
皆さん、私と一緒にきちんと座ってください。
You will connect with my gaze.
私の視線とつながってください。
I'm taking you all in.
私は皆さん全員を受け入れます。
And we're simply going to take an inhale together.
そして、一緒に息を吸い込みます。
And we exhale.
そして息を吐きます。
we inhale
息を吸い込みます
we exhale
息を吐きます
we follow the exhalation
呼気に従います
and at the end of the exhale
そして呼気の終わりに
we will slightly prolong
少し延長します
the short apnea
短い無呼吸を
we will do it voluntarily
意識的に行います
we inhale together
一緒に息を吸い込みます
you stay in this state
この状態にとどまります
and you re-inhale
そして再び息を吸い込みます
if you lose it, you exhale again
もし失ったら、もう一度息を吐きます
you observe
観察します
you re-inhale
再び息を吸い込みます
and you stay in this state
そしてこの状態にとどまります
you might observe
おそらく観察できるでしょう
we go into this end of exhale
この呼気の終わりに行くと
it's like something is suspended a bit
何かが少し中断されるような感じです
very gently
ゆっくりと
and if you observe, thoughts suddenly
そして観察すると、思考が突然
slow down
遅くなります
in fact, there's a tissue quality
実際、組織の質があります
a quality of mind that appears
精神の質が現れます
that means that in that quality
つまり、この質の中で
it's in that quality
この質の中で
that we're going to start working
私たちは働き始めます
okay, it's there
よし、そこだ
you'll see that other perceptions will arrive
他の知覚がやってくるのがわかるでしょう
okay
はい
so for that
だから、そのためには
be very attentive
とても注意深く
to the breathing
呼吸に
I simply observe
ただ観察するだけです
I observe the changes
変化を観察します
but when this state appears
しかし、その状態が現れたとき
even if there's an inhalation
たとえ吸気があっても
we can stay
私たちはとどまることができます
in this sensation
その感覚の中に
it's always there
それはいつもそこにあります
you can continue it
あなたはそれを続けることができます
like a door opening at that moment
その瞬間に開く扉のように
and you can go all the way in
そしてあなたはそこへ行くことができます
let's do it again together
もう一度、それをせずにやりましょう
you connect well
よくつながってください
with the spirit
精神と
of that one
その人の
he's always in it
彼はいつもその中にいます
so you inhale
そうやって息を吸い込みます
now we're going to do it
今からやります
we're going to complicate it a little bit
少し複雑にします
we're not going to take a voluntary breath
それは、意図的な呼吸をしないということです
We're going to observe our normal breathing and you're just going to be
私たちは通常の呼吸を観察し、あなたはただ
attentive to
注意深く
settle into this space. Keep your eyes open, stay
その空間に身を置きます。目を開けたまま、私と一緒に、ここにいて、
with me, here, fix your gaze
そこに焦点を合わせます
on this gentleman's eyes. Inhale,
この男性の視線に。息を吸い込み、
observe your breathing.
呼吸を観察します。
Then we exhale.
そして息を吐きます。
When we exhale,
息を吐くとき、
at the end of the exhalation,
呼気の終わりに、
a small door opens.
小さな扉が開きます。
You settle there,
あなたはそこに身を置きます、
like a child sitting down.
座る子供のように。
Thoracic breathing
胸式呼吸は
is truly triggered at the moment of birth.
誕生の瞬間に真に始まります。
The opening before.
以前の開口部。
makes small diaphragmatic movements,
小さな横隔膜の動きをします、
but it's not yet.
しかし、まだです。
That means the breath of life
それは生命の息吹が
is before that moment.
その瞬間よりも前にあるということです。
And so, when we enter there,
ですから、そこに入っていくとき、
we will seek to work on the breath.
私たちは息吹に取り組もうとします。
And there, it's an entry point
そして、それは入り口です。
to, I'm giving you a key,
鍵を差し上げます。
to enter into this perception of the breath.
この息吹の知覚に入るための鍵です。
After that, we'll go even further.
その後、さらに深く掘り下げていきます。
Because after that, we'll look for
なぜなら、その後、私たちは
the balance points in primary respiration
一次呼吸におけるバランスポイントを探しに行きます。
to find the points of silence
沈黙のポイントを見つけるために、
or the problem of emotion.
あるいは感情の問題を見つけるために。
intelligence can resurface in the pathways of transformation.
知性は変容の道筋の中で再び現れることができます。